I have stated several times that
dub Digimon is the greatest animated series of all time.
But uh.. After rewatching it..
I feel like..
It needs a promotion. To best series of all series.
[sounds of garbage truck loading or unloading I don't even]
This is a sequel to my previous video.
Do you have to watch it now?
Gonna.. Recap my recap right now.
[clears throat for garbage retrospective inception]
AND ON THE EIGHTH DAY, GOD CREATED DIGIMON.
But he did not have a VHS player.
But weeks later, he sends a prophet
to Elijah ForKids to tell him to dub it.
What's it about?
Seven kids are at a summer camp, in Japan.
So a tsunami shows up.
Izzy: "We've been transferred to a digital world,
we're in a goddamn isekai!"
Digimon: "Hello, we are Digimon. We can evolve to sell more toys."
Izzy: "Hello Digimon..."
".. Let's go starve in a desert."
I hope this doesn't become a thing.
Joe and Matt: " Hey, a hotel."
SixPackumon: "Hehe."
SixPackumon: "It's not a hotel. It's an illusion."
SixPackumon: "By me, a digimon with 5% body fat"
SixPackumon: "I will now split you up."
Angelmon: " No you will not!"
Angelmon: "Time to get penetrated."
SixPackumon:" Aaaah, let me tell you about internet security."
Izzy: " We defeated SixPackumon."
Izzy: "Let's go starve in a desert again."
"Why did we decided to do this, what was the plan?"
Etemon: "Hello kids it's me."
Etemon: "Monkey Elvis."[explodes]
Matt: "Ah. He died of constipation"
"Ah. A black hole."
"Ah. It sucked in and killed Tai"
M-Maybe, consider watching the previous video.
Or rewatch it. It has layers.
When we last saw everyone, Tai died.
Now, Tai isn't dead. He wakes up and he is back in Tokyo.
No. This is the American dub.
Back in..
Nebraska. It's still August 1.
Which means time in the Digi-World moves faster.
Why's that? Quick question: What's 8 times 8?
I bet you had to pause the video and think about that for a couple of minutes.
But a computer can solve it in less than a minute.
Hey,his sister Kari is home.
They turn on the TV and learn that no one else can see that
Digimon are mass killing humans.
Kari: " I told mom and dad and they said:"
"Sweety. Eat you schizophrenia medication."
Now I am miserable.
Then Digimon start attacking, destroying stuff, a hole opens up in the sky.
Which sucks in all the rubble.
Which must be look for the people watching, but
the Japanese are usually pretty overworked, so they probably blame that.
Also Dino and Tai get sucked in.
Baack to the Digi-Woorld, and of course we're stuck in a goddamn desert again
Plant some trees dumb Digimon!
First guy they meet is mini-Breadmon, hasn't evolved in weeks.
Apparently they split up,because they were worried they would eat each other
Matt and TK find an amusement park
which without employees is really just a bunch of murder devices.
Good thing Matt was there to stop the kid from doing something stupid.
So he left. And then
Pre-SixPackumon:" Ha, I'm pre-SixPackumon"
TK:" Can you look for my brother?"
Pre-SixPackumon: " Sure thing kid."
Pre-SixPackumon: "I'm back. Your brother's dead. I'm your new guardian"
Tofu thinks he's lying because, look at him.
And the bat rightly calls him racist.
TK doesn't want bigoted Pokemon,and leaves.
The bat. Is actually evil. Finds two wolves with amnesia
Pre-SixPackumon: "Ah. These are Cosby-shrooms."
The four meet up.
TK: " Are you gonna apologize to Batmon?"
Patamon: " I would never apologize to a black Digimon!"
Bat serves them mushrooms but Dino, while taking a diggy shit,
finds the same mushrooms.
and someone behind the bush warns him.
HEY HEY HEY
Plan foiled.
Episode ends with the bat apologizing to the next big bad.
Sure not appearing in this episode.
Weeks earlier, Joe found a random restaurant and decided to eat here
because this was before reviews.
Turns out, the restaurant exclusively accepts US dollars, but he only has
N-Neb-Neb.. Nebraskan Yen.
Joe is now an indentured servant.
Matt's here.
And the egg manager tells him: " If you leave I"ll kill your friend."
"Oh. You are clearly evil, let's fight!" :
Is what a sane person would say. Instead he accepts.
So they work for weeks, and the other dude show up.
Tai: "Eh Joe, why aren't you just leaving? What's he gonna do, call the cops?"
Matt:" Oh yeah."
Then the egg beats the shit out of them, and is only defeated when Tigermon evolves into..
.. Post-Apocalyptic-Furrymon
Izzy is getting the Nobel prize winning procedure of
lobotimization. True story.
I already talked about this episode in one of my not Digimon videos.
Reunited, yeaah.
Every episode in this ark ends with the bat talking to big bad number 3.
Who is clearly, an absolute moron.
He keeps sending the one guy who is always failing.
A palace, full of frogs and sperm being worked to death.
Who is treating them like video game developers?
Mimi!
They tell her to leave and she throws her friends in jail.
Thinking the best way to deal with them is wheel execution.
But why are the frogs so loyal?
Frog: "Our guard is asleep,"
" and the only thing that will wake him up is a beauutiful vooice."
Mimi: " Hi froggies. This is a song I like to sing when I'm feeling sleepy!"
[clears throat]